-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=cece&飞飞=-
-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
制作: 飞飞
校对: cece
LOVE
-=cece&飞飞=-
老爸老妈浪漫史
第1季 第22集
How.I.Met.Your.Mother
Season 1 Episode 22
2006年5月的纽约
It was the May of 2006 in New York city
不错的生活
and life was good.
似乎将有所改变
But everything was about to change,
...你们觉得如何?
So... what do you think?
又是Robin?
Robin again?
Ted
Ted,
这个宇宙明显不想让你和Robin在一起
the universe clearly does not want you and Robin to be together.
不要触怒它
Don't piss off the universe.
宇宙会扇你的脸
The universe will slap you.
相比于我的感情生活宇宙是不是要关注些更重要的?
Don't you think the universe has more important things to think about than my dating life?
除非你的感情生活是维系整个宇宙的关键...
Unless your dating life is the glue holding the entire universe together...
哇...好冷
whoa. Chills.
你们不觉得冷吗?
Anybody else get chills?
我知道,我已经走过这条路
Look,I realize we've been down this road before,
可是,不管我怎么走
but the fact is,whatever I do
都会回到Robin这里
it all keeps coming back to Robin,
所以...我必须这样做
so... I gotta do this.
搞什么?
Ow! What the hell?
不是我
That wasn't me.
是宇宙
That was the universe.
值得一提的是,在这个非常时刻
the funny thing was at that very moment
宇宙确实在做一件事--
the universe was working on something--
风暴
a storm.
热带风暴"威利"将来到我们身边
so tropical storm Willy is going to be with us
最晚周一
at least until Monday.
届时将有一场满天猫狗的大雨
It's gonna rain cats and dogs,folks.
所以,小心别踩到狗狗
So don't step in a poodle.
Sandy? Robin?
谢谢,Lou
Thanks,Lou.
呀,太糟了
Boy,too bad.
这周末都市新闻1频道本来有个露营活动
Our Big Metro News One camping trip was going to be this weekend.
是啊,冒着大雨露营? 算了吧 好脏啊...恶
Yeah,but camping out in the rain? No fun. Muddy. Yuck.
这次是真的要"因雨推迟"了
Guess we'll have to take a rain check.
明天再和各位见,纽约
And we'll check in with you tomorrow,New York.
有个愉快夜晚
Have a great night.
结束
And,we're clear.
失败
Bummer.
我本希望这个周末能和你上床,Scherbotsky.
I was hoping to finally have sex with you this weekend,Scherbotsky.
有必要重申下"不和同事睡觉"的政策
Well,I'd give you the "I don't date coworkers" speech again,
上帝,这次请务必让这贱人记住啊
but,god,you must have that sum'bitch memorized by now.
虽然有点可惜
Shame,though.
今晚的节目很带劲
It was a pretty hot show tonight.
最后那一段我们一唱一和
The rhythmic give and take of our improvised banter there at the end
令我血脉贲张
really got my freak juice flowing.
他说的有道理
Dude,he's right.
你这样屡败屡战,什么时候是个头啊?
How many times do you have to watch this crash and burn before you say,"enough"?
再一次,再多试一次
One more. One more time.
再来一次惊天动地的浪漫表白
One more big,beautiful,stupid romantic gesture.
然后,不管她说什么,是或否
And then,whatever she says, yes or no,
就这样了,如果她答应,固然好
that's it. If it's yes,great.
不答应,我就永远放弃Robin
If it's no,then I am done going after Robin forever.
惊天动地的浪漫表白是怎么样的?
So what's this big,beautiful romantic gesture?
我要给她准备一份...
I am going to make her...
混音CD
a mix CD.
不,开玩笑的,我心里有数
No,I'm kidding. I got a plan.
Lily,我需要Robin公寓的备用钥匙
Lily,I'm gonna need the spare key to Robin's apartment.
我知道怎么回事了
I see where this is going.
Ted,涂满奶油躺在女孩的床上 是没有用的
Ted,waiting naked in a girl's bed wearing whipped cream undies does not work
...也有例外
... usually.
场地: Martha的葡萄园,1999年
The setting--Martha's vineyard,1999.
角色: 在下和一位黑发的国际交换生 她的名字叫...
The characters: Yours truly and a raven-haired au pair by the name...
宇宙
universe.
你这计划到底怎么样的?
So,this plan you speak of?
记不记得我和Robin第一次出去?
Remember the first night Robin and I went out?
我给她偷了一个圆号
I stole a blue French horn for her
差点就得手了
and it almost worked.
是啊,哥们
Yeah. Dude,
那招很牛
that was awesome,
你怎么可能超越那次?
but how are you ever going to top that?
她很快就到了
She should be here any second.
呃...我们很饿
Uh,we're pretty hungry.
你什么时候给我们叫匹萨?
When do we get our pizza?
不要老是...我们迟些会要匹萨的,好不好?
Enough with the... we'll go get pizza later,all right?
只要...
Just...
妈的
Damn it.
喂
hello.
嗨,Lily,我被锁在房门外了
Hey,Lily,I'm locked out of my apartment.
我到你那里去拿备用钥匙
I need to come pick up my extra key.
备用钥匙?
Extra key?
我有你家的备用钥匙?
Do I have an extra key to your apartment?
有,我给你的
Yes,I gave it to you.
哦,对啊...钥匙
Oh,right. That key.
我弄丢了
Yeah,I lost it.
完了,只能找锁匠了
Great,now I gotta go to the locksmith.
不,等等...
No,wait,uh...
你可以试试敲门
maybe you should just knock.
敲门?
Knock?
Lily,我的狗还没那么能干
Lily,my dogs aren't that well trained.
你好Lily,我是旧金山拉塞尔艺术基金会的Janet Kagan
hello,Lily,this is Janet Kagan at the Russell House Art Foundation here in San Francisco.
很高兴通知您,您的夏季奖学金申请被核准了
I'm pleased to inform you that we've accepted your application for our summer fellowship.
尽快给我们回复,再见
We look forward to hearing from you. Bye-bye.
哦,Robin,我-我要挂了
Uh,Robin,I-I gotta go.
敲门,好不好?
Just knock,okay?
夏季奖学金?
Summer fellowship?
敲门
Just knock.
好吧
Okay.
嗨
Hi.
Robin...
我已经说过了
I've sort of said this already.
差不多说出来了
I mean I've half said it.
我想说,就是说的很差
I've tried to say it,and I've said it badly.
所以我来了,来向你说
So this is me,just saying it.
弦乐伴奏
With strings.
我为你痴迷
I'm crazy about you.
我认为我们应该在一起
I think we should be together.
你说怎么样?
What do you say?
what do you say?
好
Yes.
不好
No.
不知道
I don't know.
这三个是备选
Those are the three options.
Ted,这有点太...
Ted,this is so...
我知道
I know.
我回家准备看电视"Jeopardy"
I come home,I was going to watch Jeopardy
结果家里有一个弦乐四重奏而且...
and there's a string quartet and...
我要尿尿
I have to pee.
哦,不好意思
Oh,I'm sorry.
去吧...我们...我们等你
Un,go ahead. we'll...uh, we'll wait
我们事先说好的是...
Yeah,cause when we talked earlier,
你说了有匹萨的
you said there'd be pizza.
不,我说结束之后有匹萨
No,I said I'd get you a pizza afterwards.
你看,能不能暂时不谈这个?
Look,could we talk about this later?
我的爱情正在紧要关头
I'm sort of professing my love here.
当然
Sure.
不会有什么匹萨了
We're not getting any pizza.
好了
Okay.
我们谈谈
let's talk.
好的
Okay.
嗯...
Um...
你们要不要休息一下?
oh,hey,you guys want to take five?
谢谢各位,只要一小会儿
Thanks,guys. Just need a minute.
面临重大决定
Sort of a big life decision.
不过我喜欢蓝色乐器
Love the blue instruments,though.
我们的内部笑话
Kind of an inside joke.
谢谢
Thanks.
你疯了
You're crazy.
是的
Right.
别这样
Come on.
我也不是没想过
It's not that I haven't thought about this.
你知道我想过的
You know that I have,
让我们面对现实好不好?
but let's look at this,okay?
我们刚开始恢复朋友关系
We only just started being friends again.
我知道...可是...
I know. But... come on.
我们要的东西不一样
And we want different things.
这一点没有改变,还是老样子
That's still there. That's not going away.
如果我们这么做了
I mean,what if we do this
结果却不如意
and it doesn't work out
连朋友都做不成了?
and I'd lose you as a friend?
我要好好考虑
I gotta think about this.
好吧,没问题
Okay,fine.
在飞机上考虑吧
Think about it on the plane.
我们这个周末去巴黎
Let's go to Paris for the weekend.
我说真的
I'm serious.
玩笑
I'm kidding.
真的
I'm serious.
我不能去巴黎,我要去野营
I can't go to Paris,I'm going camping.
我以为取消了
I thought that thing was canceled.
现在又恢复了
Well,it's back on.
什么时候的事?
Since when?
大约1小时前
Since like an hour ago.
...把风暴推回了大西洋
...Sending the storm back out into the Atlantic.
周末将是晴空万里
So it's blue skies this weekend.
Sandy? Robin?
谢谢Lou,但还是有一点小小的乌云
Thanks,Lou,but that blue sky isn't without at least one cloud.
我很遗憾地宣布,从今天开始一周后
I'm sorry to announce that one week from today
我将离开都市新闻1频道
I will be leaving Metro News One.
每晚为大家播报新闻是我的荣幸
It has been an honor to bring you the news each night,
早晨读报纸也是
and read the paper to you each morning.
我会珍惜这段经历
I will always treasure it.
晚安,纽约
Good night,New York.
结束
And we're clear.
你要走?
You're leaving?
没错,我辞工不干了
There. I quit my job.
现在我们不是同事
We're not coworkers.
这下你能和我一起吃晚饭了吧?
Will you please have dinner with me?
我说笑的
I'm joking.
我在CNN找到工作了
I got offered a job at CNN.
哦,恭喜
Oh,congratulations.
也恭喜你
Congratulations yourself.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
这样的
Well,
Joel问我谁可以接我的班做主播
Joel asked me who I thought should replace me as lead anchor.
我告诉他是你
I told him you.
他们下周会宣布,装的惊讶点
They're announcing it next week. Act surprised.
哇哦
Wow.
谢谢
Thanks.
还有,好的
And,yes.
什么好的?
Yes,what?
好的,我们去吃晚饭
Yes,let's go get dinner.
不如就定在这周末的野营?
How about this weekend on the camping trip?
我烤出一根真诚的香肠
I roast a mean weenie.
你不是说真的吧
Oh,you're kidding me.
不要,你别去
No way. Don't go on this thing.
Ted,我肯定要去
Ted,I have to go.
是公司的露营活动
It's a company camping trip.
是吗? 因为这听起来像一次约会
Really? Because it also kinda sounds like a date.
和Sandy...以及他的小香肠
With Sandy... and his weenie.
你能说这不是?
I mean is this not a date?
我...我不知道
I don't...I don't know.
怎么了? 难道你喜欢那个家伙?
So,what? You actually like this guy now?
我不知道
I don't know.
你要和他勾搭在一起?
Are you gonna hook up with him?
我不知道
I don't know.
不,你知道
Yes,you do.
不,Ted,我不知道
No,Ted,I don't.
你知道吗? 我无所谓
And you know what? That's okay.
我不像你一样,把将来的每一分都计划好
I don't plan out every second of my life like you do.
- 我没有计划...
- 哦,是吗?
- I don't plan out every...
- oh,really?
这算什么?
What is all of this?
你就不能简单地说
I mean,why can't you just say,
"嗨,Robin,一起去吃寿司?"
"hey,Robin,let's go get some sushi?"
不,你非要弄个乐队还有巴黎
No,it has to be a-a string quartet and-and Paris
鲜花巧克力,还有厮守终生
and flowers and chocolates and let's spend the rest of our lives together.
你不觉得我们的关系应该超过寿司了吗?
Don't you think we're a little bit past sushi at this point?
天啊,你畏惧真实的生活
God,you are so terrified of anything real.
你就像漂浮在空气中
It's like you're floating out in space.
脚踏实地吧,Robin
Touch the ground,Robin.
回到真实中来,犯个错误
Live in the world, make a mistake.
犯这个错
Make this mistake.
我要好好想想
I need to think about this.
可以
Fine.
不,对不起,我...
No,I'm sorry,I...
我不能再这样下去
I can't do this anymore.
我需要答案
I need an answer.
如果你要我马上就说同意,我...
If you want me to say yes right now,I...
我不能
I can't do that.
好吧,如果不说"是"
Well,if it's not yes,
那就是"否"
then it's a no.
也许我们真的没有缘分
Then I guess it's not meant to be.
你努力了,兄弟
Nice,try,buddy.
场面很劲爆
Good hustle out there.
想想好的一面
Look at the bright side.
至少你可以了结了
At least you got some closure.
她作出了选择,你可以继续前行了
She's made her choice and you can finally move on.
去他妈,这事没完
Screw that. This ain't over.
Ted,你坐在这里宣布的...
Ted,you sat here in this very booth and you said...
不管我说过什么
I don't care what I said.
我一定要成功
This is gonna happen.
她不能说没有缘分
She can't say it's not meant to be.
我们注定要在一起
It is meant to be,
知道为什么?
and you know why?
因为我决定要在一起
Cause I mean it to be.
取消暂停?
Unpause?
取消暂停
Unpause.
让我们暂停
Let's pause.
是这样的,Marshall和Lily吵架的时候 有一条规矩
See,Marshall and Lily had a rule that at any point during a fight
他们可以暂停休息一下
they could pause and take a break.
他们的战争经常持续数天
Their fights often lasted for days.
油画奖学金?
A painting fellowship?
我原本就不会去的
I was never going to take it.
- 在加州?
- 我原本就不会去的
- In California?
- I was never gonna take it.
Ted,她要去参加露营了
Ted,she is going on that camping trip.
有本事你就阻挡天意
Dude,barring some act of god,
否则Robin将和Sandy共度周末
Robin's gonna be with Sandy this weekend.
好吧
Fine.
如果必须要对抗天意
If an act of god is what it takes,
那就对抗天意吧
then an act of god it is.
你说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
我要让它下雨
I'm gonna make it rain.
我不会坐视Robin和那个家伙去出游
i can't let Robin go camping with this guy.
怎样才能阻止这一切?
So how do I keep that from happening?
简单――下雨即可!
Simple-- I make it rain!
Ted,你想让我再扇你一下吗?
Ted,do you want me to slap you again?
上次扇的还蛮过瘾的
Cause I kind of enjoyed it the first time.
听着,也许我疯了...
Look,I-I might be crazy right now...
不对,你知道吗? 我绝对是疯了
no,you know what? I am definitely crazy right now,
但是我有计划
but I have a plan.
你以前约过的那个女孩,Penelope,
That girl you used to go out with,Penelope,
她是不是土著文化方面的博士?
wasn't she getting her PHD in native american culture?
是
Yeah.
你和她还有联系吗?
Are you still in touch with her?
当然,虽然我们不在一起做爱
Sure. I mean,even though we stopped having sex,
我们还是经常相聚,每月一次,聊天叙旧
we still get together,like,once a month to chat and catch up,
当然我们没有联系了!
and of course I'm not in touch with her!
那好,你要重新和她取得联系
Well,you're gonna need to get in touch with her.
我要她教我怎么跳祈雨舞
She's gonna teach me how to do a rain dance.
- 你是说"祈雨舞"?
- 是的
- Did you just say a "rain dance"?
- Yes.
- 祈雨舞
- 是的
- A rain dance.
- Yes.
祈求下雨的舞蹈
A dance to make it rain.
是的
Yes.
要找到Penelope!
We're finding Penelope!
我才不去!
No,we are not!
要去!
Yes,we are!
Ted,不要逼我做"理性"的代言人
Ted,you're forcing me to be the voice of reason
我不适合代言理性!
and it's not a good look for me!
我为什么要帮你?
Why the hell should I help you?
别这样,尽管我们两个没有结果
Come on,I know it didn't work out between us,
但是我们...还是有过一段情
but we did...have a relationship.
我们在你的车里做过两次
We had sex twice in your car,
然后你甩了我
and then you dumped me.
这也叫一段情?
How is that a relationship?
做了两次!
Twice!
Barney,我不可能...
Barney,there is no way...
嘘!
shh!
说真的,好吗
seriously,come on.
Penelope,我需要这个周末下雨
Penelope,I really need to make it rain this weekend.
为什么?
Why?
有一个女孩子...
There's this girl...
"有一个女孩子"
"There's this girl."
你懂吗,传统的祈雨是对自然的神圣的崇拜
You know,the traditional rain dance is a sacred prayer to nature.
伟大的神明不会帮某些白人泡妞
I don't think the great spirit looks too kindly on white dudes who co-opt it to get laid.
Penelope,这个女孩子是我爱着的
Penelope,this is the girl I love.
如果这个周末不下雨
If it doesn't rain this weekend,
她就要和错误的对象在一起,求你
she's gonna end up with the wrong guy. Please.
这个错误的对象
This wrong guy,
- 是不是超级坏蛋?
- 绝对的
- is he a huge jackass?
- Absolutely.
类似Barney这样的?
Kind of like Barney?
类似
Kind of.
嗨
Hey.
你对我妈放电!
You hit on my mom!
我们又不排斥他人!
We weren't exclusive!
我帮你
I'm in.
我们一行三人来到我家屋顶
And so the three of us headed up to the roof of my building.
好的
Okay.
双腿弯曲,稍微弯下腰
Crouch down and bend over a little bit.
灌了5杯龙舌兰酒才让你摆出这个体位
Wow,it took five shots of tequila to get you in that position.
信不信把你从房顶扔下去
I will throw you off this roof.
有其母必有其女
There's so much of your mom in you.
然后她就吐个不停
And she's been throwing up ever since.
她怎么吃到这么多巧克力的?
So how'd she manage to eat so much chocolate?
还记得那个人,Ted?
Remember that guy,Ted,
我跟你提过的?
that I was telling you about?
我回家就发现他
Well,I came home and I found him
和一只乐队等在我公寓
waiting in my apartment with a string quartet
还有玫瑰和巧克力...
and roses and chocolates...
哦,太甜蜜了
oh,that's so sweet.
理论上说是甜蜜的
Okay,yes,it's sweet in theory,
是不是还有点疯狂?
but isn't it also kind of crazy?
起居室里有一支乐队--
I mean,a string quartet in my living room--
谁会做这种事?
who does that?
没人会
Nobody does that.
正是
Exactly.
不,亲爱的,没人这么做
No,honey--nobody does that.
我想我是一个无可救药的浪漫主义者
But I guess I'm just a hopeless romantic.
现在要为你的狗看病了
I'm gonna put my hand up your dog now.
这么说你要禁止我去?
So you're saying you would forbid me from going?
禁止? 谁说禁止了?
Forbid? Who said forbid?
我只是提醒你,几个月后有一场婚礼
I was just reminding you that there's this wedding coming up in a couple of months,
我想你等到那一天
and I was kind of hoping you'd save the day.
我会穿着帅气的礼服
Look for me-- I'll be the guy in the awesome suit.
好吗,Lily
Come on,Lily.
那不是你一直梦想的吗
It's what you've always wanted.
是啊,可是我的梦想还有很多
Yeah,but there's a lot of things I've always wanted,
都没有去做过
and I haven't done any of them.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我想在稳定下来之前都尝试一遍
I just need to do this before settling down forever.
现在我们从"我原本就不会去"
So now we've gone from "I was never gonna do it"
转到"我需要去做"?
to "I need to do this"?
我中途离开过吗,什么时候改的?
Did I leave the room at some point? When did that happen?
也许是你说我不可以的时候改的
Oh,maybe when you said you wouldn't let me do it.
我从来没说过!
I never said that!
如果你现在有这样的犹豫
You know,if you're having these kind of doubts now,
3个月后会有什么变化?
what's gonna change in three months?
我们干脆不要结婚算了
Maybe we just shouldn't get married at all.
那就不结
Maybe not.
- 暂停
- Pause.
你怎么样? 饿吗?
So,are you just,like,starving?
饿死了,去Red Lobster? (一家颇大型的连锁餐厅)
Totally. Red Lobster?
哦,龙虾龙虾龙虾
Oh,lobster,lobster,lobster
你真好味道!
you are delicious!
老天,我爱死奶油酱了!
Oh,god,I love butter sauce!
完美无缺
There's nothing bad about it.
我肯定你也找不出一点奶油酱的坏处
Say something bad about butter sauce,I dare you.
我找不出
I wouldn't dare.
Marshall,不
Marshall,no.
我们正在暂停期
We're on pause.
暂停的大地上没有哭泣!
There's no crying in pauseland!
暂停的地方是个仙境
Pauseland is a magical place,
有虾片堆成的山和奶油酱的河!
with-with...popcorn shrimp mountains and butter sauce rivers!
快乐快乐快乐快乐!
Happy,happy,happy,happy
快乐生日快乐!
happy happy birthday,
快乐快乐快乐快乐!
happy,happy,happy,happy
快乐生日快乐!
happy,happy birthday,
Ted,这很搞笑
Ted,this is funny.
还是搞笑
Still funny.
还是搞...现在是可悲了
Still fu...and now it's sad.
嗨,Penelope,你肯定这样跳是对的?
Hey,Penelope,you sure I'm doing this right?
应该是的
I think so.
啊
Uh-huh.
这个...真正的祈雨舞是这样的吗?
Does it,uh,look anything like a real rain dance?
应该是
I think so.
嗨,Penelope
Hey,Penelope,
你有没有亲眼见过祈雨舞?
have you,uh,have you ever actually seen a rain dance performed?
没
No.
没?
No?
我花了很大力气看资料
I've read extensively on the subject:
第一手资料,理论批评
Firsthand accounts,theoretical criticism,
还有人类学...
the anthropological...
你见过祈雨舞吗?
have you ever seen a rain dance?
我看过电影片段
I've seen a film strip.
太好了,我得走了
Terrific. Uh, look,I should run.
我要请一个看过几集ER的人给我做大脑手术
I'm getting brain surgery from some guy who's seen a couple episodes of E.R.
简直太离谱了
I can't believe this.
我们这一个小时完全是在做蠢事
We've been up here for the past hour making complete asses of ourselves.
你说"我们"是什么意思， 白人?
What do you mean "we," white man?
我们怎么会到这个地步的?
How did we get here?
几天前，我生命中最大的麻烦还是
Couple of days ago,the biggest problem in my life was,
Ted有没有吃掉冰箱里最后一份布丁
did Ted eat the last pudding snack pack in the fridge.
我想还有一块
I think there's still one left.
我的
Dibs.
取消暂停?
Unpause?
取消暂停
Unpause.
瞧...
Look...
我知道这很遭
I know this sucks.
这只是我在经历的一些事情
It's just something I'm going through.
我不是叫你去理解
I'm not asking you to understand it.
我也不是想你觉得高兴
I'm not asking you to be happy about it.
我... 我只是要你的支持
I... I'm just asking you to support it.
我想,Lily,好吗?
I want to,Lily,okay?
我真的想
I really do.
但我不能
But I just can't.
- 为什么不能?
- 因为你吓死我了
- Why not?
- Because you're scaring the hell out of me,
所以不能
that's why not.
如果你决定做个画家呢
What if you decide to go be a painter
然后你会意识到我不适合你的生活
and then you realize I don't fit in to your life anymore,
到时候三个月就变成了永远?
and three months becomes forever?
你能保证这样的事不会发生吗?
Can you promise me that that's not gonna happen?
Marshall...
你不能保证，我们现在就该分手
cause if you can't promise me that,we should just break up right now.
我不要等三个月
I'm not gonna wait around for three months
我的心会被狠狠的撕碎的
just to have my heart ripped out.
Marshall,我爱你
Marshall,I love you.
你能保证这样的事不会发生吗?
Can you promise me that that's not gonna happen?
暂停
Pause.
不,Lily,我们不能再暂停了
No,Lily,we cannot pause this anymore.
你能保证这样的事不会发生吗?!
Can you promise me that that's not gonna happen?!
暂停!
Pause!
为什么要我暂停?!
Why do you want me to pause?!
暂停功能使用的很好,宝贝
That's just a great use of the pause function,baby.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿,Ted
hey,Ted.
你在干吗?
What you doing?
祈雨
A rain dance.
伙计，你不是在祈雨
Dude,that's not a rain dance,
就像一只蜜蜂飞进胖男孩的裤子里一样
that's a fat kid with a bee in his pants.
瞧，我很怀疑一个舞蹈术的坚持者的信念
Look,I highly doubt the great spirit is a stickler for choreography.
心诚则灵
It's the thought that counts.
她还有半小时就要出发了
She's leaving in half an hour.
你正在花样年华，不要把时间浪费在一个女孩身上
These are your awesome years. You're wasting them on this girl.
这样是办不到的!
This isn't gonna work!
对，我知道
Yeah. I know that.
那你干吗还这么做?
Well,then why are you doing this?
因为我爱她
Because I love her.
我爱她!
I love her!
我们第一次约会我就告诉她了
I told her that the first night we went out,
而8个月过去了，什么都没变
and here it is,eight months later,and nothing's changed.
所以，我知道这没有用
So yes,I know this isn't gonna work.
但这必须管用!
But it has to work!
你听见我的话吗,宇宙?
You hear me,universe?
我是Ted Mosby!
This is Ted Mosby talking!
给我点雨吧!
Give me some rain!
拜托!
Come on!
拜托...!
Come on...!
哦,拜托!
oh,come on!
前锋又到达本地区
pushing the front back into the tri-state area
为曼哈顿带来了10年来最遭的一场风暴
and giving Manhattan one of its worst storms in over a decade.
怎么样?他做到了
How about that? He did it.
Robin!
嘿,Robin!
Hey,Robin!
哦,谢天谢地你在家!
Oh,thank god you're here!
下雨我的野营取消了
My camping trip got rained out.
我知道,对不起
I know. I'm sorry.
是你的错?
So your fault?
对
Yeah,it is.
下来
Come down here.
雨好大，你上来
It's pouring. You come up.
不，你得下来
No,you have to come down here.
为什么?
Why?
为什么?因为我祈来了雨 这是我今天所做的!
Why? Because I made it rain,that's what I did today!
这就够了,我已经完成了我的部分
And that's enough. I-I've done my part.
现在,下来!
Now,get down here!
我没换衣服,Ted 不,上来
I'm not dressed,Ted. No. Come up.
我不上去,Robin,不
I'm not coming up there,Robin,I'm not.
你得下来这里!
You have to come down here!
我正要...
I was gonna...
我知道
I know.
Robin和我最后在一起了
And that's how Robin and I ended up together.
原来我要做的就是让天下雨
Turns out,all I had to do was make it rain.
我早上回家时 这个城市看起来一样
as I rode home this morning,the city looks the same
人们看起来一样 一切都一样
the people looks the same it all looks the same
但是并非如此
but it wasn't
一夜间,一切都改变了
in just one night,everything is changed
老爸老妈罗曼史
第1季第22集 第一季
完
How.I.Met.Your.Mother
Season 1
End
-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
制作: 飞飞
校对: 西西
本季字幕制作结束，在此感谢西西宝贝的认真校对，第二季更精彩，敬请期待!